(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
全世界、激震！
The whole world, shaken!
あの超大作が
That blockbuster...
ついに
Finally...
スクリーンへ！！
To the screen!!
タイムリミットは24時間
Time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は 4人の「」に託された
Humanity's hope was entrusted to 4 '...'
なんだ？ここは！？
What is this place!?
どうして... こんなのひどいよ！
Why... this is terrible!
私のことはもういい！
Forget about me!
先に行け！
Go on ahead!
いろは〜〜〜〜！！！
Iroha~~~~!!!
あ〜〜！ふざけんなお前！
Ah~~! Don't screw with me, you!
なんで？
Why?
私たちの絆は...
Our bond is...
永遠！
Eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
Let's save humanity together!!
絶対に忘れないよ...
I'll never forget you...
自分史上、最高傑作です
It's my greatest masterpiece ever.
せーの
One, two...
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は......この中にいる！
The culprit is... among us!
えーー！？
Ehh!?
俺ぇ！？
Me!?
きゃーーーーー
Kyaaaaa!
これは...
This is...
背後から刀で一振り...
A single swing of a katana from behind...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective-dono, what is the matter?
怪しい
Suspicious.
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！
I can't stay in the same place as a murderer!
部屋に戻らせてもらう！
I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious.
ふふふ...
Fufufufu...
怪しい
Suspicious.
最初から最後まで...
From start to finish...
...ハラハラドキドキでしたー
...it was heart-pounding!
せーの
One, two...
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！
My name is Hakui Koyori!
どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
Just your average high school student!
ただ一つ人と違うことは...
The only thing different from others is...
科学が好き...ってところかな？
I guess that I like science?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ゥーーー！
Oh no~! I'm late, I'm late~!
きゃー
Kyaa!
いったー...
Ouch...
見ぃつけた
Found you.
一緒にいるとなんか安心するでござる
Being with you makes me feel relieved somehow.
いただきま〜す！
Thanks for the food!
ぐえっ！
Gueh!
遅い！
Late!
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The bittersweetness was exquisite!
せーの
One, two...
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた......！
Ah, you...!
holoX4周年を...
...searched for...
...検索しちゃったんですか！！！
...holoX 4th Anniversary!?
決して...
Never...
検索してはいけない...
...search for...
#SSholoX4周年
#SSholoX4thAnniv
ルイ姉...
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから...
Iroha, it's going to be okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
わ！！
Waa!!
(すごい悲鳴)
(Terrible scream)
しゅうしとりはだがたちっぱなしでしたー
I had goosebumps from beginning to end!
せーの、
Ready, and...
holoX4周年サイコー
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
La LaPaTa Pa La LaPaTa
La LaPaTa Pa La LaPaTaPa
迷宮なラビリンス
Labyrinthine Labyrinth
No招かれた招待状
An uninvited invitation
秘密で秘匿の異次元マンションへ
To a secret, concealed, other-dimensional mansion!
ガタガタのドアの笑声に
At the laughing voice from the rattling door,
No Pain, No Gain アンチェイン！
No Pain, No Gain, Unchain!
狙う魔装のホークアイ
The magic-clad Hawkeye aims,
迫る咆哮はウォークライ
The approaching roar is a war cry.
放射状に突破口もドウダロウ？の走馬灯
A radial breakthrough, what about a kaleidoscope?
Xに取り込まれてゆくよ...
You'll be swallowed by X...
刻印でござるー
It's a brand, forsooth~
不条理な見学ツアー
An absurd guided tour,
ドアからドアへイリュージョン
Illusion from door to door.
サーカス小屋よりピュアに響け笑い声！
Let laughter echo purer than a circus tent!
La LaPaTa Pa La LaPaTa...
つまり本件、
In other words, this matter,
力こそパワー的な
Power is power, like...
「迷宮なラビリンス」(Death)
"Labyrinth of Labyrinths" (Death)
並び立つシルエット
Silhouettes standing in a row.
恐怖！秒で切断Wi-Fi
Terror! Wi-Fi cut in seconds!
これまじで最恐roomだけど
This is truly the scariest room, but
刃の回廊は普通に危ないって One shot
The corridor of blades is normally dangerous, One shot,
One Kill
虚実踊るマリオネット
Marionettes dancing between truth and fiction.
堕ちる部屋は何度目？っと
How many times have you fallen into this room?
ランク外は眼中ないが落雷あかんくない？
Being out of rank isn't in my sight, but isn't lightning strike okay?
Xに取り込まれてkukuku...
You'll be swallowed by X, kukuku...
迷える子羊くんたちー！
Lost little lambs!
おさとう、スパイス、それとピンクなものいっぱいで
I've made a drink that'll get you high with sugar, spice,
ハイになれるドリンクできたよー♪
and lots of pink things~
ロックで飲んでくださいねホロックスだけに
Please drink it on the rocks, just for holoX.
ささ皆殿飲むでござるー
Come on everyone, let's drink!
吾輩酔った
I'm drunk...
いやお前が飲むんかい
No, you're the one drinking?!
じゃあとりあえず...
Well then, for now...
かんぱーい！！
Cheers!!
鏡の回廊から
From the corridor of mirrors,
帝王の冷笑警報
the emperor's cold laughter alarm.
塗り替えられる常夜に
In the eternal night that's being repainted,
爆ぜろ笑い声！
let laughter burst forth!
お前たちもな！
You too!
La LaPaTa Pa La LaPaTa...
重なる
Overlapping...
嵩んで声を高らかに
Pile up and raise your voices loud!
ラッパッパ ダダ ラッパッパ
Rapapa dada rapapa
停電の海を越えるため
To cross the sea of blackouts,
つまり本店 腹痛が痛い？
In short, the main store... my stomach hurts?
ぶち破れ 行くの Super Future
Break through! We're going to the Super Future.
Party Labyrinth Please
Bye Bye
はーい！
Yesss!
ということで！
So with that said!
holoX...
4周年！
4th Anniversary!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congrats! Congrats!
イェーイ！
Yaaay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
張り切っていくぞー！
Let's give it our all!
オー！
Ohhh!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を...
So, let's hear our ambitions for future activities...
早いね展開。
Things are moving fast.
早いね。
It's fast, isn't it?
じゃあルイから。
Let's start with Lui.
えっ私から！？
Eh, me!?
お願いしまーす。
Go ahead.
どうしようかな、えー...
What should I say? Um...
えーと、みんなありがとう！
Um, thank you everyone!
えーと、どうしようかな... えー...
Um, what to do... uh...
5年目も...
In the 5th year too...
頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best!
holoX 頑張るぞ！
HoloX will do its best!
イェーイ！
Yaaay!
こよちゃん！
Koyo-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
えー、この5年目は、4人で団結力をもっとグッとして...
Um, for this 5th year, the four of us will strengthen our unity even more...
グッとして！
Strengthen it!
そろそろ日本征服ぐらいはしていきたいなと！
It's about time we achieve at least Japan domination!
確かに。
That's true.
いいライン、いいライン。
Good line, good line.
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど...
The world is still a bit difficult...
日本征服頑張ります！
But I'll do my best for Japan domination!
いくぞー！
Let's gooo!
はい！いろは氏！
Yes! Iroha-shi!
はい！みなさん、ごー！
Yes! Everyone, Go!
ご？
Go?
ござるの「ご」！
The 'Go' of Gozaru!
ということで5年目もね、元気に健やかに健康に活動頑張っていきたいと思います！
So, for the 5th year too, I want to do my best in activities energetically, wholesomely, and healthily!
holoX 5周年頑張るぞ！
HoloX 5th Anniversary, let's do our best!
5年目ね。
5th year, you mean.
5年目頑張ろう！
Let's do our best in the 5th year!
5周年まで頑張ろうまた。
Let's work hard until the 5th anniversary.
じゃあ私いいっすか？
Then, can I go?
今年も... 生き残るぞ！
This year too... I will survive!
大事！生き残るね。
Important! Surviving, huh.
生き残れた今年も。
We survived this year too.
そして！
And!
来年こそ！5年目こそ！
Next year for sure! In this 5th year!
我々の年にするぞ！
We will make it our year!
するぞー！
We will--!
ちょっとダサい...
A bit lame...
待ってダサい！？
Wait, lame!?
なんでなんで？みんな同じやん！
Why? Everyone did the same thing!
こよりの高さがどうでもいいです。
Koyori's height doesn't matter.
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Just look at this, everyone!
ライブステージ！！
Live stage!!
すげー！！
Amazing!!
めっちゃカッコ良くない？
Isn't it super cool?
最初のさ、登場からさ、うちらカッコ良かったね！
From the very beginning entrance, we were cool, right!
カッコ良かったっしょ？
We were cool, right?
カッコ良かった！
It was cool!
しかもですね、このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて、
Moreover, this stage is not just big,
色んな仕掛けがありますので！
it has various mechanisms!
なになに！？
What, what!?
注目して！なんかね、出てきたりとか...
Pay attention! Something might pop out...
出てきたり！？
Pop out!?
上がったりとか！
Or go up!
すごい！
Wow!
シッポが上がってんだわ。
My tail is going up.
変形したりとかさ！
Like transforming!
合体とかさ！
Or combining!
いや、さすがに無理だろ。
That's impossible, obviously.
合体！？
Combine!?
合体したい！
I want to combine!
あるんじゃないの？
Maybe there is?
合体はやりたかったんですけど...
I wanted to do combining but...
ちょっとさすがにholoX、予算が少なく...
But as expected, HoloX's budget is a bit low...
5年目の給料もっといいよね！？
Our 5th-year salary will be better, right!?
でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん！
But we made this stage, so it's fine!
ということで5年目もholoXのみなさん、ぜひこんな我々ですけどよろしくお願いします！
So, everyone who supports HoloX, please continue to treat us well in our 5th year!
お願いします！
Please!
ちなみにここで...
By the way, right now...
お知らせなんでございます！
We have an announcement!
お知らせだよ！
It's an announcement!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると...
If you join the Hololive official channel membership...
なんと！限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので、
Surprisingly! You'll be able to use limited emoji stamps,
ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
so please use them in the comments to hype things up!
打て打てー！
Type them, type them!
さらに！なんと今日からもうひとつメンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども！
Furthermore! It seems there's one more membership perk starting today!
なんと！先日発表した新曲「スキデカ」と「プライベート・アイズ」の壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
You can also get wallpapers for the new songs 'Sukideka' and 'Private Eyes' announced the other day!
マジ！？欲しい！
Seriously!? I want them!
俺たちが欲しい！
We want them!
策士…？
Strategist...?
重要な…
Important...
森…森…森…
Forest... forest... forest...
盛りだくさんらしいので
Since there seems to be plenty in store,
最後までちゃんと見ていくように
Please make sure to watch until the very end.
途中退室禁止です
Leaving halfway is prohibited.
よろしくお願いします
Thank you very much.
森！森！森だくさん！
Forest! Forest! Plenty (Mori-dakusan)!
森の字を作り…
Making the character for 'forest'...
混ぜろよ！
Let me in!
ちょっと待ってください
Wait a minute, please.
もう早くしないと
If we don't hurry up,
皆に見せらんないからライブ
We won't be able to show everyone the live.
早速 最初は
Right away, first up is...
こよちゃんのパートから！
Starting with Koyo-chan's part!
イェーイ！
Yeaaaaah!
見ててね！
Watch me!
見てるよ！
We're watching!
早く！
Hurry!
行くぜ！
Let's go!
爆ラブ＋ケミストリー
Baku Love + Chemistry
ラブ湧き発生
Love bubbles up suddenly
存在実体マジ感
Existence, reality, serious feeling
調合は未完成
The mixture is incomplete
ときめきのケミカル
Heart-pounding chemical
どうなるほど
What will happen? Indeed
そんじゃこれならどうかと
Then how about this?
日進月歩だラブラボラトリー
Steady progress in the Love Laboratory
泡立つこのエモーション
This bubbling emotion
混ぜるほどに甘くなるなる
The more I mix, the sweeter it gets
過剰なモーション
Excessive motion
奇跡的に愛しくなれ
Miraculously become beloved
フラスコにハート
A heart in the flask
やべなってあっーと
Oh no, wait
効果の程
The extent of the effect
君が一番
You are number one
ほら僕と君なれ
Look, become [one with] me and you
ちょっと危険な混ぜ混ぜ
A slightly dangerous mixing
ドッカンだケミストリーだ
Boom! It's Chemistry!
曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Vague you, chromatography
平和恋のジェネリック
Peaceful love's generic
もっと夢中になれなれ
Become more and more obsessed
水金地火木 僕の胸
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, my heart
ギューって仕留めたい 君の胸
I want to capture your heart tightly
ランダムな振幅グラファー
Random amplitude grapher
爆誕君とケミストリー
Explosive birth, chemistry with you
僕の甘い溶液
My sweet solution
溶けるくらいドキドキするはず
It should make your heart pound enough to melt
白い煙吐いで
Breathing out white smoke
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない
Not that type of heart-pounding
けどまあある意味成功かな？
But well, maybe it's a success in a way?
ラブは不溶性
Love is insoluble
勉強も手につかん
I can't even focus on studying
調合は試作中
The mixture is in prototype phase
だんだん脳はトビ跳ね
Gradually my brain is jumping
どこいく？
Where are you going?
そんなトライ＆爆発
Such a try and explosion
君と重ねてくテレレテッテ
Layering with you, terere tette
急と冷めさせた薬の味
The taste of the medicine that suddenly cooled
ラブで夢見る君が一番
You dreaming of love are the best
中毒症状過多ですか
Is it an overdose of addiction symptoms?
僕が君のアンチドート
I am your antidote
ドッカンだケミしたりない
Boom! Not enough chemistry
曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Vague you, chromatography
平和恋のジェネリック
Peaceful love's generic
どんな僕も観測してさ
Observe any version of me
ドッカンだ君プラスハート
Boom! You plus heart
溶けて混ざっちゃうシナジー
Melting and mixing together, synergy
君こそが愛のアトミック
You are the atomic of love
もっと夢中になるなる
Becoming more and more obsessed
水金地火木 僕の胸
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, my heart
ギューって仕留めたい 君の胸
I want to capture your heart tightly
ランダムな振幅グラファー
Random amplitude grapher
爆誕君と追加検証
Explosive birth, additional verification with you
水金地火木 僕の胸
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, my heart
ギューっとして僕の胸
Squeeze my heart tightly
ランダムな振幅グラファー
Random amplitude grapher
爆誕君とケミストリー
Explosive birth, chemistry with you
実験は君と永遠なり
The experiment is eternal with you
君が好きってこの感情に
By this emotion called 'I love you'
潰されてる
I am being crushed
足りないのはどちらの方が
Which one is lacking?
どうでもいいかも
It might not matter
傷ついたって知らないよね
Even if you notice, you don't know, right?
責任とって
Take responsibility
興味ないよ
I'm not interested
最低んなったあの娘のほうがいいんだもんね
You'd rather have that girl who hit rock bottom, huh?
あたし興味ないよ キミなんて
I'm not interested in you at all.
マジ半端ないね
You're seriously unbelievable.
ダメダメね
You're hopeless.
Love Me Gimme Chuなこの愛に
Love Me Gimme Chu, by this love...
壊されたい
...I want to be destroyed.
Ah 壊されたい
Ah, I want to be destroyed.
止め処ないよキミの愛を独り占めしたい
It's endless, I want to have your love all to myself.
毒だろうがなんだろうが抱きしめてあげたい
Poison or whatever it is, I want to embrace it.
ナンセンス契約 独占のFALLING LOVE
Nonsense contract, a monopoly of falling love.
逃さない ずっと
I won't let you get away, ever.
キミが好きってその感情に
That feeling that I like you...
騙されてる
...I'm being deceived by it.
大事な法はキミが確か
The important rule is that you...
決めかねてる
...are hesitating to decide.
バカすぎるキミへ
To you, who are too stupid.
あたし興味ないよ キミなんて
I'm not interested in you at all.
ただ振り回して好きなだけ
I'm just stringing you along as much as I like.
LOVEでDEEPなこの愛は
This love that is love and deep...
渡さないから
...I won't hand it over.
バカだよね 色ボケだね
You're an idiot, blinded by lust.
それ見たことか ザマァみろか
Didn't I tell you? Serves you right.
もう他でもない あなたに呪われたまま
Cursed by none other than you.
まぁ
Well...
いや興味ないよ キミなんて
No, I'm not interested in you.
バカなフリしてあげただけ
I just pretended to be stupid for you.
愛と哀をぶつけ合って
Clashing love and sorrow together...
ぐちゃぐちゃになって
...it all becomes a mess.
あたし興味ないよ キミなんて
I'm not interested in you at all.
マジ半端ないね ダメダメね
You're seriously unbelievable. You're hopeless.
Love Me Gimme Chuなこの愛に
Love Me Gimme Chu, by this love...
壊されたい
...I want to be destroyed.
Ah 壊されたい
Ah, I want to be destroyed.
見た目だけじゃ分からない
You can't understand just by appearances.
私のこと可愛いだけと
That I am just cute...
まさか思っていないよね
...you don't really think that, do you?
私のホント
My true self...
知っていてほしい
...I want you to know it.
予測不可能な範囲で
Within an unpredictable range,
不測の事態も動じない
I'm unfazed even by unforeseen situations.
ポーカーフェイスでいるけど
I keep a poker face, but...
心は常に青白く燃える
...my heart is always burning pale blue.
諦めはしない 媚びたりもしない
I won't give up, and I won't fawn.
私は負けない
I won't lose.
扱いやすい奴だとなら
If you assume I'm easy to handle...
甘く見ると痛い目見るよ
...you'll regret underestimating me.
それでも時には逃げ出してしまいたい
Even so, sometimes I just want to run away.
そんな衝動に弱音吐き出す夜もある
There are nights I vent my complaints from such impulses.
ほんの小さな小さな妥協が
Just a tiny, tiny compromise...
降り重なり重なって動けない
...piles up until I can't move.
大きな大きな可能性失くし
Losing big, big possibilities...
未来を狭めてしまうから
...because it narrows down my future.
どんなに暗くても辛くても
No matter how dark or painful...
後悔だけはしない
...I won't regret anything.
生きてる意味は誰じゃなくて
The meaning of life isn't 'who'...
生き方なんだ
...it's 'how to live'.
現実逃避 理想との距離を
Even if I could shorten the distance...
縮められたとしても
...between escaping reality and my ideals,
ポーカーフェイスでいるだけ
I'll just keep a poker face.
何事もなかったかのように
As if nothing happened.
立ち止まりはしない 後戻りもししない
I won't stop, and I won't turn back.
夢も捨てない
I won't throw away my dreams either.
らしいとか
Like 'that's like you'...
自分探し
Searching for myself,
それでも時には
Even so, sometimes,
温もりが恋しい
I miss the warmth.
そんな感情に流されて
Swept away by such emotions,
迷子になる夜もある
There are nights when I get lost.
こんな甘い甘い言葉だけ
Just seeking such sweet, sweet words,
求めてしまうような弱さはいらない
I don't need the weakness that makes me crave them.
痛い痛い経験だって
Even painful, painful experiences
私を強くしてくれるから
Will make me stronger.
これが これが私の
This, this is my...
本当
Truth.
とても狭い狭い世界の中だけで
I don't want to let it end
終わらせたくはないんだ
Just inside this very narrow, narrow world.
広い広い世界の果てまで
To the ends of the wide, wide world,
駆け抜けて生きてくんだから
I'm going to run through and live.
時には気が済むまで
Sometimes until I'm satisfied,
楽しんでやるさ
I'll enjoy it.
イケてるのは見た目じゃなくて
It's not my looks that are cool,
生き方なんだから
It's my way of life!
はい 注目
Yes, attention!
アレもコレもソレも多分タブー
This and that and that too are probably taboo.
わかってんの？ What is 常？
Do you get it? What is normal?
プースカパースカ 愚痴愚痴じゃナンセンス
Snoozing and grumbling is nonsense.
わかってない！
You don't understand!
後悔がBestie 狭心症Capacity
Regret is my Bestie, angina Capacity.
ビビりじゃ負けない比じゃない あげる絶句ビンタ
I won't lose in fear, no comparison, I'll give you a speechless slap.
表面上だけ Always 漂白してもね
Even if you always bleach just the surface, you know?
食べたいの 痛いの 飛んでけないくらい
I want to eat, it hurts, so much I can't fly away.
称賛 圧巻 脳細胞で 能ない鷹は爪出しましょう
Praise, masterpiece, with brain cells, let the hawk with no skill show its claws.
高まって参りましょう
Let's get hyped!
アタシ アナスタシスガール
I am Anastasis Girl.
不滅 量産型 女 (Satan!)
Immortal mass-produced woman (Satan!)
だから Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちにのさんで Dan Dan Dan
One, two, three, Dan Dan Dan.
アナスタシスガール 昨日 イジメた 罰
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying yesterday.
君は Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へ Dan Dan Dan
To hell, Dan Dan Dan.
革命 Go-Live
Revolution Go-Live!
アナスタシスガール... Girl...
Anastasis Girl... Girl...
お口チャック
Zip your mouth.
みんなで花いちもんめ
Everyone play Hana Ichi Monme.
あの子が欲しい
I want that kid.
相談しよう そうしよう
Let's consult, let's do that.
健やかなるときも病めるときも
In sickness and in health,
絶対よ
Absolutely.
人間らしくあれ
Be human-like.
微伸び調節が 怠慢
Fine-tuning is negligence.
Die or Die or Die or Die...
Die or Die or Die Ahh!
痛いの 痛いの
It hurts, it hurts,
飛んでけないならば
If it won't fly away,
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ 青春だ
Do it, say it, it's youth.
目には目を 致してやりましょ
An eye for an eye, let's do it to them.
アタシ アナスタシスガール
I am Anastasis Girl.
無礼講のお時間
It's time for a free-for-all.
だから Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちにのさんで Dan Dan Dan
One, two, three, Dan Dan Dan.
アナスタシスガール 極めて遺憾です
Anastasis Girl, it is extremely regrettable.
君は Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へ Dan Dan Dan
To hell, Dan Dan Dan.
革命 Go-Live
Revolution Go-Live!
アナスタシスガール... Girl...
Anastasis Girl... Girl...
ああ お願い放っといて
Ah, please leave me alone.
お願い放っといて
Please leave me alone.
とびきりの嘘と嘘が飛び交う中で
In the midst of extraordinary lies and lies flying around,
真実となるのは
What becomes the truth
果てが生み出したゾンビだって
Are zombies created by the end.
アタシ アナスタシスガール
I am Anastasis Girl.
不滅 強さがタギる
Immortal strength boils.
だから Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちにのさんで Dan Dan Dan
One, two, three, Dan Dan Dan.
アナスタシスガール 昨日 イジメた 罰
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying yesterday.
君は Nan Nan Nan Nan Nan
What, what, what, what, what are you?
地獄へ Dan Dan Dan
To hell, Dan Dan Dan.
革命 Go-Live
Revolution Go-Live!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl.
スキじゃないスキじゃない？あ〜
Not love, not love? Ah~
タラッタッタ タラッタッタ タラララララ
Tarattatta Tarattatta Taralalalala...
ラブのリポート 冷めやらぬ感情
A report on love, feelings that won't cool down.
バカじゃないの 目を覚まして
Are you stupid? Wake up!
全然平常心で 興味と過信だらけ
Totally calm, full of interest and overconfidence.
さらけ出してウォンチュ
Expose it all, want you.
近付くと出来なくて困る 矛盾なベイビー
Trouble is I can't do it when I get close, contradictory baby.
でもたまに構ってあげる
But I'll pay attention to you sometimes,
クセになっちまう
it'll become a habit.
絶妙な距離感 ゲーム
Exquisite sense of distance, a game.
知覚 近付く
Perception, getting closer.
一生デカクデカクデカクデカク
For a lifetime, huge, huge, huge, huge!
なんでもちょーだい 差し出すスキ作りましょ
Give me anything, let's make a love we can offer up.
それがライクなのか
Is that 'like'?
ラブなのか
Is it 'love'?
はたまた両方なんでは
Or maybe it's both?
ナシ
None.
アリ
Exist.
ナシ
None.
絶対アリだろ
Definitely exist, right?
そしてデカクデカクデカクデカク
And huge, huge, huge, huge!
とにかくデカクデカク
Anyway, huge, huge!
いや全部叶うからね
No, everything will come true.
結局重い内緒
After all, it's a heavy secret?
なんか乗らないわ
I'm just not into it.
大胆にやってきましょ
Let's do it boldly!
スキはデカク スキデカク しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Love is huge, love huge, please bear with us for a while.
スキ！デカ！スキ！デカ！
Love! Huge! Love! Huge!
スキ！デカ！スキデカ スキ！
Love! Huge! Love huge, Love!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Convey lots of feelings to everyone.
俺だけに見せてくれたって いいなぜひいなぜ
It's fine to show only me, it's fine, it's fine.
１人と区別 サービスは出来ません！
I can't distinguish just one person for service!
それでもいいかな
Is that okay though?
もっと知りたいことだらけ
Full of things I want to know more.
ほどほどにして
Keep it in moderation.
でも知らないほうが幸せか
But maybe ignorance is bliss?
どっちかにしてよ
Make up your mind!
絶妙な距離感
Exquisite distance,
ゲーム
game,
バランス
balance,
取り合う
vying for each other.
一生つかず離れずつかず離れず
For life, not too close not too far, neither attached nor apart.
ちょうどよく塩梅で
Just the right balance.
お互いもっと分かり合えたら
If we could understand each other more,
特別になれる
we can become special.
いつも通じ合える
Always communicating.
この先は想像できないけど
I can't imagine what lies ahead though,
結構いい感じかも
might be a pretty good feeling.
ギリギリでもいいか
Is barely okay fine?
そのまま進みます
Proceeding as is.
踏みつけていきます
I'll trample through.
ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたいね
I want to discuss our future here.
まだいらないでしょ
We don't need that yet!
いいからほら！
It's fine, come on!
Three, two, one, Let's go!
一生 Let's go 二人
For life, Let's go, the two of us!
一生デカクデカクデカクデカク
For life, huge, huge, huge, huge!
なんでもちょーだい 差し出すスキ作りましょ
Give me anything, let's make a love that we offer up.
それがライクなのか
Is that 'like'?
ラブなのか
Is it 'love'?
はたまた両方なんでは
Or maybe it's both?
ナシ アリ ナシ
None, exist, none.
絶対アリだろ
Definitely exist, right?
そしてデカクデカクデカクデカク
And huge, huge, huge, huge!
とにかくデカクデカク
Anyway, huge, huge!
いや全部叶うからね
No, everything will come true.
結局重い内緒
A heavy secret in the end?
なんか乗らないわ
I'm just not into it.
大胆にやってきましょ
Let's do it boldly!
一生つかず離れずつかず離れず
For life, not too close not too far, neither attached nor apart.
ちょうどよく塩梅で
Just the right balance.
お互いもっと下らないことでも
Even if it's silly things between us,
ワイワイやってたい
I want to have fun,
付き合っていたい
I want to keep hanging out.
この先も変わらない関係性を
A relationship that won't change in the future too.
ちょっと行き過ぎて
Going a bit too far,
またちょっと全身後退？
Retreating the whole body a bit again?
ひとマス進みます
Move forward one square.
さんマス戻ります
Move back three squares.
スキはデカク スキデカク しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Love is huge, love huge, please bear with us for a while.
不思議な関係 お見知り置きを
A strange relationship, pleased to meet you!
超常現象 Tenderness
Paranormal phenomenon, Tenderness.
東奔西走 Timeless
Running around, Timeless.
でも劣等感？
But an inferiority complex?
ほら最強じゃん
Look, we're the strongest.
今焼き付けろ
Burn it in now.
超常現象 Tenderness
Paranormal phenomenon, Tenderness.
東奔西走 Timeless
Running around, Timeless.
我ら名探偵
We are great detectives.
いや迷探偵？
Or lost detectives?
Pa pa pa pa pa pa
満月の夜くぐり抜けて
Passing through the full moon night,
ビルの隙間まで溜息を
sighing even into the gaps of buildings.
骨の髄まで探し出して
Searching to the marrow of the bone,
深い闇へ誘うの
inviting you into the deep darkness.
逮捕令状 秘密の Show Time
Arrest warrant, secret Show Time.
有言実行 世界を制夜
Executing words, conquering the night.
オレンジに染まってゆく崩壊
The collapse dyed in orange.
君のためにメラメラ
Burning for you, mera mera.
愛を燃やせメラメラ
Burn the love, mera mera.
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
From that day I swore to protect it through.
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning for tomorrow, mera mera.
その音に乗っちゃえば
If you ride on that sound,
退屈なんて無縁でしょサヨナラ
boredom is unrelated, goodbye.
超常現象 Tenderness
Paranormal phenomenon, Tenderness.
東奔西走 Timeless
Running around, Timeless.
でも劣等感？
But an inferiority complex?
ほら最強じゃん
Look, we're the strongest.
今焼き付けろ
Burn it in now.
超常現象 Tenderness
Paranormal phenomenon, Tenderness.
東奔西走 Timeless
Running around, Timeless.
我ら名探偵
We are great detectives.
いや迷探偵？
Or lost detectives?
Pa pa pa pa pa pa
映画照らす欲望の影を
The shadow of desire illuminating the movie,
忍び寄せて欺いて
creep up and deceive.
震える手を握りしめよ
Grasp the trembling hand.
変化完膚なきまでサイケデリック
A transformation, thoroughly psychedelic.
厨二ラッシュで短期チョコレート
A chuunibyou rush with short-term chocolate.
劣等感は置き去りで
Leaving the inferiority complex behind.
夢のためにメラメラ
Burning up for the sake of the dream.
闇を燃やせメラメラ
Burn the darkness, flare up!
どんな時もこの声を届けたい
I want to reach you with this voice, no matter when.
崖っぷちでメラメラ
Burning up on the edge of the cliff.
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up.
大どんでん返し 奇跡のおまじない
A huge reversal, a miraculous spell.
電光石火 S.O.S
Lightning speed, S.O.S.
君のためにメラメラ
Burning up for you.
愛を燃やせメラメラ
Burn the love, flare up!
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Since that day I swore to protect it to the end.
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning up for tomorrow.
この音に乗っちゃえば
If you just ride this sound,
退屈なんて無縁でしょ サヨナラ
Boredom has nothing to do with us, goodbye!
超常現象 Fantastic
Supernatural phenomenon, Fantastic.
東奔西走 Princess
Busy rushing about, Princess.
超常現象 Fantastic
Supernatural phenomenon, Fantastic.
東奔西走 Princess
Busy rushing about, Princess.
Ba Ba Ba Ba Ba Ba
ぬぬぬぬ...
Nu nu nu nu...
ライブさ、めっちゃ良かったよね？
The live was super good, right?
めっちゃ良かったね！
It was super good!
めっちゃ楽しいね！
So much fun!
まだ終わってないけどね
It's not over yet though.
まだ終わってないよ
Not over yet.
これからが最高だよね
The best part starts now, right?
なんだこれ？
What is this?
なんやこれ？
What's this?
ん？
Hm?
あ！ 気付いちゃいました？
Ah! You noticed?
バレバレだよ！
It's totally obvious!
変じゃない？ めっちゃかっこいいじゃん！
Isn't it weird? No, it's super cool!
こよが作りました！
Koyo made it!
また経費使ったんかお前
Did you use expenses again?
これ吾輩の給料...？
Is this from my salary...?
いやいやいや...
No no no...
これが何だろうが給料同じだからね
Whatever this is, the salary stays the same, okay?
ええ！？
Eeeh!?
ということでこれは、告知用カードをもう...
Anyway, this is... for the announcement cards...
めくるだけ！
We just flip them!
アピール早っ！
That pitch was fast!
告知だ！
Announcement!
なんだこれ？
What is this?
告知ー！
Announcement!
ということでこの流れでね、グッズ紹介でございますね
So, following this flow, it's time for the goods introduction.
いーね！
Nice!
あ、今回はそういう感じね？
Ah, so it's that kind of vibe this time?
はい、ということで
Yes, exactly.
はい、じゃあ私からね、いきますよ
Okay, then I'll start us off.
はい、holoX活動4周年記念グッズ
Yes, holoX Activity 4th Anniversary Goods,
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade
今日の18時より販売開始されております！
On sale starting today at 18:00!
パチパチパチ！
(Clapping)
それではそれぞれ見ていきましょう
Now let's look at each item.
まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙、ドン！
First up, the Premium Acrylic Shikishi, boom!
イェーイ！ 今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です
Yay! This acrylic shikishi uses this event's Key Visual.
なんと複製サインとロゴが箔押しになってて
And guess what, the replica autographs and logo are foil-stamped,
めっちゃいい感じじゃん！
making it look super nice!
かっこいい！
So cool!
いいじゃんいいじゃん！
Nice, nice!
そしてお次はこちら、ホロカ・スリーブ！
And next up is this, Holoca Sleeves!
このカードがまさにそれなんですけど
These cards we have here are exactly that.
キービジュアルを使ったホロカ・スリーブです
They are Holoca Sleeves featuring the Key Visual.
こちらなんと60枚入り！
This pack contains a whopping 60 sleeves!
ワオ！
Wow!
やったぜみんな！
We did it guys!
なんぼあってもいいですからね
You can never have too many of these.
ホロカに使いやすいですね
Easy to use for Holoca.
そして！ アクリルスタンド！
And! Acrylic Stands!
オイ！ 元気だねえ！
Oi! So energetic!
めっちゃかっこいい我々でね
Looking super cool, aren't we?
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで
These feature different expressions from the Key Visual design,
是非アクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいね
so please try comparing them with the Acrylic Shikishi.
気持ち悪っ
Gross.
帰ってきた帰ってきた
She came back, she came back.
かわいいねー
Cute~
強そうですね
Looks strong.
そしてこちら！
And here!
記念メダル！
The Memorial Medal!
記念メダルも発売しております
We are also selling Memorial Medals.
なんとケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます
It's a medal that comes with a case and a drawstring pouch.
かわいいー！
Cute!
こちら期生毎でデザインが異なっておりますので
Since the design differs for each generation,
なんと今回はholoXだけのデザインになっております
this time it's a design exclusive to holoX!
是非是非ゲットしてよーくチェックしてみてください
Please get one and check it out closely.
なんか騒がしいな...
It's kinda noisy here...
そのドリルやめろ、そのドリル
Stop with that drill, that drill!
ヘイヘイヘイ！
Hey hey hey!
はい！ということで次は何のカードかな？
Okay! So what's the next card?
カードちゃん！
Card-chan!
あるのね
There is one, huh.
オープン！
Open!
ということでタイミーコラボ！
So, it's the Timee Collaboration!
タイミーだタイミー！
Timee, it's Timee!
やってましたねー
We did that, didn't we.
先日タイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけども
It's about the rare part-time job we recruited for on Timee the other day.
現地の様子があるということで
We actually have footage from the site!
見てみましょう！ どうぞ！
Let's take a look! Go ahead!
ドン！
Boom!
お！？
Oh!?
すげー！ なんかholoXがいる！
Amazing! holoX is there!
holoX推してる！
They're promoting holoX!
配ってる！
They're handing them out!
配ってくれてるー！
They're distributing for us!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you everyone!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
他にもありますよ！ ドン！
We have more! Boom!
え？ ここもいたの！？
Eh? They were here too!?
あの有名なあの娘！？
That famous girl!?
すごーい！
Amazing!
めっちゃ見られてる！
People are totally watching!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
お！え？待って待って。
Oh! Eh? Wait, wait.
新宿？あれ後ろにも写ってる？
Shinjuku? Is it shown behind us too?
え、あれ聞いてた？あれ聞いてた？
Eh, did you hear about that? Did you hear?
え、あれ嘘嘘嘘。
Eh, that's a lie, lie, lie.
聞いてないよ！
I didn't hear about this!
今日のあの、21時前に流れていたあのよく分からない映像...
That confusing video that was playing before 9 PM today...
あのよく分からない...
That confusing...
おい！流れちまったのかよ！
Oi! It already played?!
大丈夫か？
Is that okay?
あれ怒られるんじゃ...
Won't we get in trouble...
なんかもっとさ、なんかかっこいいMVとかさ、あるだろ！
There should be something cooler, like a cool MV or something!
そうだよな、ライブ映像とか流したらもっと...
Yeah, if they played live footage, it would be more...
なんで、なんでこれなんだよ！
Why, why is it this?!
まあ良かった...え、でもありがとう！
Well, it was good... eh, but thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
やったー！
Yay!
はい！ということでこちら、
Yes! So, regarding this,
応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
how many applications do you think we received?
300！
300!
でもさ、お仕事だからね。お仕事だからやっぱり100...
But, it's a job, you know. Since it's a job, maybe 100...
500人とか来てくれてるかな？
Maybe 500 people came?
そうだよね。平日だもんね。
That's right. It is a weekday.
300いないくらいじゃないか？
Maybe less than 300?
大変だからね。
Because it's tough work.
なんと！
Surprisingly!
数千人の応募が来たということです！
We received several thousand applications!
すごすぎる！
That's too amazing!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
え？驚きすぎだろ。
Eh? You're too surprised.
驚きすぎだろ。
You're too surprised.
ええー！？そんなに！？
Ehh!? That many!?
数千人！？
Several thousand!?
誰か給料貰ったせいで...
Because someone got paid...
給料貰ってるていで決まってるよ。
It's decided on the premise that they get paid.
あの大丈夫、あのいろはよりも多めに渡してます。
Um, it's okay, I'm handing out more than Iroha.
やめてよ！しっかりと...福利厚生...
Stop it! A proper... welfare program...
タイミーさんですからね。
Because it's Timee-san.
あ、タイミーさんね。
Ah, Timee-san, right.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや、選ばれし9人のみんなもありがとうな！
Also, thank you to the chosen 9 people!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
やったー！
Yay!
そして、次はなんだ？
And, what's next?
はい！
Yes!
あ、オープン！
Ah, open!
こいこいこいこい！なに来る？
Come on, come on! What's coming?
あ、来た！
Ah, it's here!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
あ、タワー！
Ah, tower!
タワーコラボだ！
It's a tower collaboration!
俺がタワーになるぞ。
I'll become a tower.
タワーということで！皆さん！
Speaking of towers! Everyone!
タワーコラボ、もう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
The tower collaboration info is already out, but look here!
こちら！
Here!
全国4箇所で行われる「holoX Tower Invasion」！
'HoloX Tower Invasion' will be held at 4 locations nationwide!
イェーイ！
Yay!
明後日の12月4日から開催されます。
It starts the day after tomorrow, December 4th.
お！
Oh!
えー、さっぽろテレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力MIRAI TOWER、梅田スカイビルで開催されますので、
It will be at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER, and Umeda Sky Building,
ぜひ皆さん行ってくださいね！
so please everyone, go check it out!
行ってね！
Go there!
イェーイ！
Yay!
俺たちがタワーだ！
We are the tower!
タワーだ！
Tower!
おい！混ぜろ！
Oi! Let me in!
混ぜろ！
Let me in!
今回大事なことがあるんですけど、ちゃんと予約をしないとですね、
There is something important this time. Without a proper reservation,
あの皆さん入れないんで、事前予約必須です。
you can't enter, so advance reservation is mandatory.
あ、そうなんだ！
Ah, really!
そうなんです。事前予約ね、忘れてる人もえー、多分いると思うので、
That's right. I think there might be people who forgot to book in advance,
え、死ぬなあ。
Eh, you'll die.
その場で行っても入れないらしい。
Apparently you can't get in if you just show up.
はいれないんです。
You can't get in.
ちゃんと予約をするように！
Make sure to book your reservation!
しとかな！しとかないと！
Gotta do it! Gotta do it!
ぜひお願いしますよー！
Please do it!
うん。
Yeah.
しとかないと。
Gotta do it.
よしじゃあ、解体解体！
Alright then, disassemble, disassemble!
すごいね。
Amazing.
おばあおばあ。
Grandma, grandma.
タワーだね！
It's a tower!
はい、次！次！
Okay, next! Next!
次！
Next!
あ、次いー！
Ah, next-ii!
ドン！
Bam!
オープン！
Open!
はい！
Yes!
えー！
Ehh!
なんとなんと！ホロライブの新サービス！
Well, well! Hololive's new service!
え？新しいサービス？
Eh? New service?
うん、新しいサービス。
Yeah, new service.
ライブの感動を最速でその手に！
Get the excitement of the live performance in your hands as fast as possible!
えー！
Ehh!
おお、すごい！
Oh, amazing!
え、どういうことだ？
Eh, what does that mean?
秘密結社holoX、
Secret Society HoloX,
はい。
Yes.
4周年のライブブロマイドが、
4th Anniversary Live Bromide,
なんと！
Believe it or not!
今日のね、ライブの写真が明日から、
Starting tomorrow, photos from today's live
コンビニでプリントアウトできるんだって！
can be printed out at convenience stores!
えー！
Ehh!
リアルの手に入るんだ！
You can get them for real!
そうなんだよ！
That's right!
すごい！
Amazing!
で、対象店舗はファミリーマート、
And the participating stores are FamilyMart,
うん。
Yeah.
ローソン、
Lawson,
うん。
Yeah.
ミニストップになります。
and Ministop.
イェーイ！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you!
いっぱいある！
There's so many!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
え、いいの？
Eh, is it okay?
どこでも...
Anywhere...
そして、今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです。
Also, it seems you can pre-purchase online starting now.
おお、マジ？
Oh, seriously?
便利だ！
Convenient!
ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら、
However, starting tomorrow you can also choose photos at convenience stores
えー、購入することもできるみたいなので、
and purchase them there,
詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
so please check the link on the bottom left for details!
こっちこっちこっちこっち！
Here here here here!
こっちこっちこっち！
Here here here!
この辺！
Around here!
さらにですね、今回はそちらのお写真にですね、ブロマイドに、
Furthermore, this time on those photos, on the bromides,
うん。
Yeah.
私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけれども、
it seems you can add our messages to them,
え！？ついてくんの！？
Eh!? They come with it!?
すごい！デコれる？
Amazing! Can we decorate?
え、いいの！？
Eh, is it okay!?
そう！
Yes!
聞いてないよ！
I didn't hear about this!
あ、来た来た来た！
Ah, here it comes!
今から書く、そうです。
We're going to write it now, apparently.
えー！？
Ehh!?
ちょっと待って！急すぎないか！？
Wait a minute! Isn't this too sudden!?
すいません。
Sorry.
ここでやるの？
Doing it here?
浮いてる！浮いてる！
It's floating! It's floating!
しかも、考えてないけど、まあまあまあまあ...
Also, I haven't thought of anything, but well well well...
ここで書くんだ。
So we write here.
考えて書いてください。
Think and write, please.
はい！
Yes!
え、はい！
Eh, yes!
座ってやー。
Sit down.
え、全部？何個あんのこれ？
Eh, all of them? How many are there?
はい！
Yes!
時間もね、迫ってますからね。
Time is running out, you know.
早く書くんですよ。
Write quickly!
にょにょにょにょ。
Nyo-nyo-nyo-nyo.
でも別々に...
But separately...
意外と集中力必要だね。
This needs more concentration than expected.
私繋げ！
I'll stall!
オッケー！
Okay!
安牌安牌で。
Playing it safe, playing it safe.
書けた！
Wrote it!
早！
Fast!
早くね？
Isn't that fast?
見して。
Show me.
ちょっと待って。
Wait a sec.
これ！
This!
あ、可愛い！
Ah, cute!
見して。
Show me.
まあ、こよこよっぽいですね。
Well, it's very Koyo-koyo.
こよっぽい。
Koyo-like.
あ、いいね。
Ah, nice.
こよっぽい。
Koyo-like.
いつまで書いてんの？
How long are you writing?
あ、いけ、みんな終わった？
Ah, go, is everyone done?
回収！回収！
Collect! Collect!
これで、スタッフさんに渡して、みんな。
Here, give it to the staff, everyone.
はい！
Yes!
お願いしますね！
Please take care of it!
ということでこれでお願いします。
So, we'll go with this.
まあみんなね、何書いたかすごく気になると思うんですが、
Well, I'm sure everyone is curious about what we wrote,
こちらのメッセージの内容は、
but the content of these messages...
みんなが...
everyone...
えっとね、私が書いたのは...
Um, what I wrote is...
あ！
Ah!
やばいやばい！
No, no!
おい！
Oi!
馬鹿野郎！
You idiot!
駄目ですよ！
You can't do that!
言わないで！
Don't say it!
みんな買ってからのお楽しみ！
It's a surprise for after they buy it!
あ、だめだ。
Ah, no good.
だめだこれ。
This is no good.
だめに決まってんだろ！
Of course it's no good!
アウトだろ！
It's out!
あ、ごめんなさい。
Ah, sorry.
ごめんなさい。
Sorry.
営業妨害だよ。
It's obstruction of business.
はい。
Yes.
そして？
And?
よし！
Alright!
よいしょよいしょ。
Heave-ho.
まだ！
Still!
残ってるよ！
There's more left!
まだ2枚もあるんで！
We still have two more!
お次はこちら！
Next is this one!
こちら！
This one!
お、オープン？
Oh, open?
なんと！あの作品とコラボ！？
What! A collab with THAT work!?
え？
Eh?
あ、なに？
Ah, what?
なになに？
What what?
あの作品？
That work?
どれだ？
Which one?
ちょっと待って、これまじ知らない。
Wait, I seriously don't know this.
どれ？
Which one?
あの作品ってなんですか？
What is 'that work'?
なに？
What?
あ、こちらをどうぞ！
Ah, please watch this!
こちらどうぞ！
Please watch this!
お！
Oh!
サテーー
Well then--
突然デハアルガ、
It is sudden, but,
或ル秘密結社ノ
Of a certain secret society
話ヲシヨウ。
Let's talk.
人間ハ、
Humans are,
＜物語＞シリーズ × holoX コラボ開催決定
Monogatari Series x holoX Collaboration Confirmed
ええー！？ うわー！
Ehh?! Whoa!
やばい！ え、いいの？
This is insane! Wait, is this okay?
え、やばすぎ！ え、めっちゃ大好きじゃんね。
This is too crazy! We love it so much, don't we?
ね、好き！ え、やばすぎる！
Yeah, love it! This is seriously insane!
え、どういうこと？ どっか行っちゃう！
Wait, what does this mean? She's going somewhere!
どっか行っちゃう！ 待って待って！
She's going away! Wait, wait!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
なんと！ マジで！？
Surprisingly! Seriously?!
え、怒られない吾輩？ 怒られないこれ？
Wait, won't I get scolded? Is this allowed?
怒られるとしたら、台本を読んでないこと！
If you get scolded, it's for not reading the script!
早く言ってよー！
Tell me sooner!
なんと「物語シリーズ」とのコラボが決定しました！
A collaboration with the 'Monogatari Series' has been confirmed!
どういうことー！？
What does this mean?!
詳細は随時発表されるようなので、お楽しみに！
Details will be announced sequentially, so look forward to it!
我々も分かっていない？
We don't understand it either?
そうなんです。本当に詳細は何も知らないんです。
That's right. We really don't know any details.
いや、ちょっとうちらも焦ってるんですけど...
Well, we're kind of panicking too...
いいんですか！？ って感じなんですけど...
Is this okay?! That's how we feel, but...
最後にひとつ、あるみたいなので、そちらに行きましょう。
There seems to be one last thing, so let's move on to that.
もう一個見ないと！ いったん動揺を...
We have to see one more! Let's settle down...
みんな落ち着けて！ 俺たちが動揺してる間に...
Everyone calm down! While we are shaking...
みなさん、この６つ目がなにか、コメントで教えてみてください。
Everyone, please tell us in the comments what you think the 6th one is.
なにかーな？ 予想して！
What could it be? Guess!
コメント見に行こう。なんかあるかな？
Let's check the comments. Is there anything?
忍ぶ... 怒られないかな？
Sneaking... Will I get scolded?
なんでこそこそしているということで、最後のひとつは皆さんなんだと思いますか？
Why are we sneaking around? Anyway, what do you think the last one is?
なんとですね、ま、ちょっとヒントを言うと...
Surprisingly, well, to give a little hint...
ま、今年２曲作りましたよね。
Well, we made two songs this year, right?
あ、作ったね。いっぱい出た！
Ah, we did. We released a lot!
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
In total, how many songs does holoX have?
何曲？ 何曲だ？ そして？
How many? How many is it? And?
え、たくさん！ 覚えてないのか！？
Eh, a lot! You don't remember?!
holoXが出してきた企画を除きますと、全部で７曲あります！
Excluding the projects holoX has put out, there are 7 songs in total!
７曲あるの！？ すごい！
There are 7 songs?! Wow!
多いね！
That's a lot!
ってことは？ もしや？
Which means? Could it be?
てかみんなわかってるか？ コメント欄わかってきたんじゃないの？
Wait, does everyone know? Isn't the comment section realizing it?
どうだ？ あ、あ！ 言ってる言ってる！
How is it? Ah, ah! They're saying it!
ということで、気付いてる人もいるみたいなので、やっぱりあちらでございます。
So, it seems some people have noticed, so it is indeed over there.
６枚目オープン！ バン！
Opening the 6th card! Bang!
なんと！ ファーストアルバムが出ます！
Surprise! Our 1st Album will be released!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しい！ ということで、ファーストアルバム...
So happy! So, the 1st Album...
『ファースト・オーダー』じゃない、『シークレット・オーダー』！
'First Order'... no, 'Secret ORDER'!
混ざったね！ 大事！
Got mixed up there! Important!
『シークレット・オーダー』だ！
It's 'Secret ORDER'!
『シークレット・オーダー』だよう！
It's 'Secret ORDER', you know!
こちらの『シークレット・オーダー』、holoXでの４年間をぎゅっと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております。
This 'Secret ORDER' is an album packed with our 4 years in holoX.
我々のデビュー曲『常夜リペイント』はオリジナルバージョンに加え...
Our debut song 'Journey Repaint', in addition to the original version...
本作のために、新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
Contains a newly re-arranged version just for this release!
なんと！？
No way?!
そしてさらに！ なんかまだ...
And there's more! Somehow still...
未発表の楽曲もあるとか...？
Are there unreleased songs too...?
８とか９とか１０とか１１とか！？
Like 8, or 9, or 10, or 11?!
増えすぎると... お楽しみ！
If it increases too much... Look forward to it!
ということでですね、通常版になるんですけれども...
So, regarding the Regular Edition...
あ、ちょっと上が見えないでーす。
Ah, I can't see the top part.
早いね！ 流れがね。
Fast! The flow is fast.
通常版には、初回限定特典があります！
The Regular Edition comes with a First Press Limited Bonus!
ああ、あるま！
Ah, Alma!
こちらでございますね。各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット４種類のうち...
This is it. Solo versions for each member, and out of 4 jacket types...
ランダムで１枚付きます！
One will be included at random!
そしてこちらですね、４枚並べると、どうやら１枚絵になるとのことですよ！
And here, if you line up 4 of them, apparently it becomes one picture!
すごい！ 繋がりそうな顔してる！
Amazing! They look like they'll connect!
ラプちゃんの角が、刀の上に来る。
Lap-chan's horns go over the katana.
あ、本当だ！
Ah, it's true!
じゃあこれ並べないと！
Then we have to line them up!
そして、完全生産限定版封入特典は...
And, the bonus included in the Fully Limited Production Edition is...
かっこよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい...
In this album full of coolness, typical of holoX...
秘密の仕掛けが？
A secret gimmick?
え、俺もわかってないぞ？
Eh, I don't know about this either?
隠されているとか！ なんだってー！？
It's hidden or something! Whaaat?!
はい、ちょっと私たちも分からないのですが...
Yes, well, we don't really know either, but...
この後２２時から、販売開始です！
Sales start after this at 22:00!
ぜひぜひご予約お願いいたします！ お願いします！
Please, please pre-order! Please!
ってことで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけれども。
So, that was a huge amount of announcements.
ま、告知カードちゃんたちはこれでお役御免ということで！
Well, the announcement cards have done their duty!
消すの！？ バイバーイ！
You're deleting them?! Byeee!
ここにね、お金かけすぎだから！ このギミックやばいだろう。
We spent too much money on this! This gimmick is insane.
消すためだけに！ 一瞬だけね！
Just to delete them! Only for a moment!
大人の力ってすげえんだからな！
The power of adults is amazing!
ということで、ライブもラストスパートでございます！
So, the live is also in its final spurt!
この後ですね、何やらちょっと、お知らせ？
After this, there seems to be some kind of announcement?
サプライズ？ があるらしいですよ？
Surprise? Apparently there is one?
最後までチャンネルはそのままで、お願いいたします！
Please stay tuned to the channel until the end!
ワクワク！ じゃあみんなー！
Exciting! Alright everyone!
最後まで、楽しんで！
Enjoy it until the end!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
そこに跪け！
Kneel down right there!
掃いて捨てるような現実を
The reality you cast aside like trash...
一刀両断 叩き斬れ！
Slice it in two with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ
You children lost in endless reincarnation,
漆黒の翼で誘おう
Let me invite you with jet-black wings.
我ら エデンの星を統べる者
We are the ones who rule the Star of Eden,
秘密結社...
Secret Society...
holoX！
holoX!
でござる！
Is here!
常夜リペイント
Jouya Repaint
あーあ どうしようもないこの世界
Ah, this hopeless world...
どうしてほしい？
What do you want me to do?
真っ赤な終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The deep red bell signaling the end tolls.
Ba-ba-ba-da-do-wa Let's trip しようぜ
Ba-ba-ba-da-do-wa, let's take a trip.
陰キャも陽キャも sing a song
Introverts and extroverts alike, sing a song.
気持ちいいことだけが全て
Feeling good is everything,
落ちてゆく闇の底へ
falling to the bottom of the darkness.
甘い甘いメロディ
A sweet, sweet melody.
ほらどうぞどうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Here, go ahead, towards the clapping hands.
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えろ
repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう 全て
If you wish for it, I'll give you everything.
常識破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense!
狂う狂う狂い倒せ
Go crazy, crazy, madly defeat it all!
火をつけろ
Light the fire!
全てを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything completely!
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you a secret.
悪のカリスマ 導くぜ完璧さ
The charisma of evil, I'll lead you to perfection.
正義とか知らないし ケジメ鳴らして誘い
I don't know about justice, settling scores and inviting you.
真面目に不真面目？ 弊社の通過儀礼
Seriously unserious? Our company's rite of passage.
望み求め 願い叶え 世界征服！
Desire, seek, grant wishes, world conquest!
Ba-ba-ba-da-do-wa Let's trip しようぜ
Ba-ba-ba-da-do-wa, let's take a trip.
退屈な世界へ Bye-bye-bye
Bye-bye-bye to the boring world.
覚めることのない夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream you'll never wake from.
ほら お眠りなさい
Here, please go to sleep.
もっともっと奥へ
Deeper and deeper,
ほらどうぞどうぞ 行きたいでしょ
here, go ahead, you want to go, right?
もう止められない
You can't stop anymore.
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in evil,
世界を塗り替えろ
repaint the world!
望むもの与えよう 全て
I'll give you what you desire, everything.
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules!
来る来る回し尽くせ
Spin, spin, keep spinning it all!
焼き尽くせ
Burn it all down!
全ての紛い物へ
To all the fakes out there...
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you a secret.
ついに4周年！
Finally, our 4th anniversary!
狂気の宴の始まりだ！
Let the feast of madness begin!
貴様ら！準備はいいか！？
You lot! Are you ready!?
括目せよ！
Witness us!
holoX！
holoX!
手を上げろ！
Hands up!
いろは！
Iroha!
叫ぶでござる！
Scream!
こより！
Koyori!
踊って！
Dance!
世界を手にする holoX！
The world in our hands, holoX!
世界を変えてく holoX！
Changing the world, holoX!
ルイ姉！
Lui-nee!
もっと！
More!
ラプラス！
Laplus!
最後は全員行くぞ！
Everyone, one last time, let's go!
holoX！
holoX!
世界を手にする holoX！
The world in our hands, holoX!
世界を変えてく holoX！
Changing the world, holoX!
世界はこの手に holoX！
The world is in our hands, holoX!
心を解き放て
Release your heart.
ほらどうぞどうぞ 身を任せて
Here, go ahead, surrender your body.
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えろ
repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう 全て
If you wish for it, I'll give you everything.
常識破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense!
狂う狂う狂い倒せ
Go crazy, crazy, madly defeat it all!
火をつけろ
Light the fire!
全てを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything completely!
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you a secret.
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社holoX
We, the ones who rule the Star of Eden, Secret Society holoX
いくぞー！ holoX！
Let's go! holoX!
で、ござる！
De, gozaru!
機は熟した
The time is ripe.
常闇より現れし 英霊たちよ
O heroic spirits emerging from the everlasting darkness.
準備はいいか！
Are you ready?!
Ohhhhh!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー
LaPaPa LaPaLaPa LaPaPa
ラパタ ラパタ ラッパッパー
LaPaTa LaPaTa LaPaPa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
The night deepens, look, darkness.
能ある鷹はPONで隠す
A wise hawk hides its talons with clumsiness.
何したがへエゴイスティング
Do what you want, egoisting.
Noとニンニン サムライガール
Saying 'No' and Nin-Nin, Samurai Girl.
闇金しないけど
I don't do loan sharking, but...
フルベットでしょ借金借金
It's a full bet, right? Debt, debt.
征服すればOK
It's OK if we conquer.
切り裂く赤字借金借金
Slashing through the deficit, shwing, shwing.
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
On the palm of evil, you'll want to dance.
ほら君も 気付けばノリノリです
Look, before you know it, you're grooving too.
どうしようもない
It can't be helped.
Don't show no mind
堕ちてく運命
A destiny falling down.
ならしょうがない
Then there's no choice.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's just repaint everything.
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
X and X and X and X...
交差する真ん中で
In the center where they cross.
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト
Next and Next and Next and Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun.
Jan! Wo-oh-oh-oh-oh
飛びな 飛びな
Jump, jump!
闇が呼ぶ方へ
To where the darkness calls.
Wo-oh-oh-oh-oh
暗黒のエクスデス
The dark Exudes.
混沌としたこの世界を
This chaotic world...
我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ
...we will repaint in holoX colors.
皆の者、かかれ！
Everyone, attack!
Yes My Dark!!!
「完璧漆黒(アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ)」
Absolute Darkness Infinity.
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my grasp!
魔眼 ホークアイ！
Demon Eye, Hawk Eye!
お前もholoXの一員となるのだ
You too will become a member of holoX.
頼りになるママ
The reliable mom.
これで君もコヨリにメロメロだ
With this, you're madly in love with Koyori.
静心なく花の散るらむ
Restlessly, the flowers fall.
一刀両断 叩き斬る！
Cutting in two with a single stroke, slash!
どうしようもない
It can't be helped.
Don't show no mind
堕ちてく運命
A destiny falling down.
ならしょうがない
Then there's no choice.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's just repaint everything.
括目せよ！！
Witness this!!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
X and X and X and X...
交差する真ん中で
In the center where they cross.
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト
Next and Next and Next and Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun.
Jan! Wo-oh-oh-oh-oh
飛びな 飛びな
Jump, jump!
神が呼ぶ方へ
To where God calls.
Wo-oh-oh-oh-oh
笑うのは
The ones laughing...
holoXです！
...will be holoX!
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー...
LaPaPa LaPaLaPa LaPaPa...
12.01
SECRET ORDER
機ハ熟シター
The time is ripe.
全テノ"holoXer"ヘ告グー
Announcing to all "holoXers".
集へ、決戦ノ地ー
Gather at the battleground.
2026.4.29
PIA ARENA MM
1st MISSION
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
Are you ready to take the world in hand?
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
The banquet of madness begins.
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
#SSholoX World Repaint Plan
やったーー！！
We did it!!
やばーい！！
That was crazy!!
やったー！現地！
We did it! In-person!
皆も驚いてくれてる？
Is everyone surprised too?
いかがでしたか？
How was that?
やばいね、早いよ！
It's crazy, it's so soon!
ということで
So, with that said,
なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
Our in-person live concert has been decided!
やったーー！
Yay!!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ファーストミッションや！
It's the 1st Mission!
ということで、みんなそれぞれね、感想とライブに向けて抱負をお願いしたいと思います
So, I'd like to ask everyone for their thoughts and aspirations for the live concert.
はい。うん。
Yes. Yeah.
決まったな。
We nailed it.
決まったね。
いや、めちゃくちゃね...
Man, seriously...
あの、デビューの時から「ライブやりたいね」って...
We've been saying we want to do a live since our debut...
言ってたし...
...talking about it...
デビュー前から。
Since before our debut.
うん。
Yeah.
それが... もうありがたいことにね...
And that... thankfully...
みんなの協力のおかげで、ホロックサーさん達の応援のおかげで...
Thanks to everyone's cooperation and the support of the HoloXers...
うん。
Yeah.
叶いました！やったー！
It came true! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
えー、もう... ホロックスの... みんなで...
So, uh... with everyone in HoloX...
うん。
Yeah.
当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので。
We want to hype it up on the big day.
ぜひみんな遊びに来てください！
Please come and see us!
かっこいいホロックスを見に来てね！
Come see the cool side of HoloX!
見に来てねー！
Come see us!
はい、ということで...
Okay, so with that...
続いては、じゃあ、こよ！
Next up, Koyo!
はい！
Yes!
えー、今言ってた通り、みんな「ライブやりたいね」って話もしてたし。
Uh, like we just said, we've talked about wanting to do a live.
やっぱこよは、一番忘れられない風景が、初めてのフェスで...
For Koyo, the most unforgettable scene was at our first Fes...
ホロックスでやった時の...
...when HoloX performed...
あの... ジョウヤリペイントで... 会場がもう「ワーッ！」ってなってくれたの...
...with that joy-filled paint... and the whole venue went "Wah!"...
浴びた時...
...when I basked in that.
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで。
I really can't ever forget that.
やっぱり、その... 今度はね、ホロックサーさん達だけの会場...
So, you know... this time, a venue just for HoloXers...
俺たちの会場で！
In our own venue!
やれるわけじゃないですか！
We get to do it there!
俺たちの箱で！
In our own box!
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
I am so incredibly happy!
で、できて、本当にこの... やらせてくれることにしてくれた大人の皆さんにも...
And, being able to do this... to the adults who let us do this...
大人の皆さん！
To the adults!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
なので、この４人の出来る力を全て出して。
So, we will give everything the four of us have got.
そして歌とダンスもね、より一層力を込めて！
And we'll put even more power into our singing and dancing!
やっていきますので！
We're going to do this!
絶対現地！そして現地来れない人は映像でも！
Definitely come to the venue! Or watch the video if you can't!
絶対見に来てください！よろしくお願いします！
Please definitely come see us! Thank you!
お願いしまーす！
Pleaaase!
はい。
Okay.
いろは氏。
Iroha-shi.
はい！
Yes!
みんな！生でござるたちの声が聴ける機会！
Everyone! It's a chance to hear Gozaru and the others live!
ホロックスのこのハーモニーが聴ける機会！
A chance to hear this HoloX harmony!
ハーモニー... ハーモニー...
Harmony... Harmony...
ハモり声、俺たちの。
Our harmonizing voices.
共鳴！共鳴が聴ける機会が！
Resonance! The chance to hear our resonance!
来たぞー！
Has come!
It's here!
いやもう本当にね、ホロックス... やっぱ本当にみんな言ってるけど...
No, seriously... HoloX... everyone's saying it but...
デビュー前からね、現地ライブをこのメンバーでやりたいって...
...since before debut, we've said we wanted to do a live with this group.
ずっと言っていたので。
We've been saying it all along.
それがやっと叶ってね、でかい声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのをね...
It's finally coming true, getting loud and hyping it up with everyone...
今か今かと楽しみに（準備）しております。
...we are looking forward to it any moment now.
我々もね、４人とも、しっかり当日までレッスンや...
All four of us will work hard on lessons until the day...
練習も含め、パフォーマンスも全部、色々みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて...
...and practice, performances, thinking of everything to entertain you all...
挑みますので！
...as we take on this challenge!
見ている皆さんも、ぜひ全力で楽しみにしつつ...
Everyone watching, please look forward to it with all your might...
そして当日は楽しんでください！
...and have fun on the day!
頑張ります！
We'll do our best!
盛り上げる準備、出来てます！
We are ready to hype you up!
出来てるぞー！
We're ready!
じゃあ最後。総帥。決めてくれ。
Lastly. My Dark. Close it out.
いや、ちょっと毎回この「最後」やめて欲しいんだよね...
Ugh, I wish you'd stop making me go last every time...
しゃーない。
Can't help it.
ちょっと、みんな、ついに...
Hey, everyone... finally...
ホロックスが... 俺たちが...
HoloX... We...
ライブー！！
Liiive!!
ライブー！
Liiive!
もうみんなはさ... すごい「ライブやりたい、音楽大好き」みたいな...
Everyone's been like "I want to do a live, I love music"...
ずっと聞いてたからさ。俺は嬉しいよ。
...I've heard it forever. So I'm happy.
いやもちろん、当事者よ？私も好き。
I mean, of course, I'm involved too, right? I like it too.
やっぱりライブがね、一番楽しいから。
Live shows are the most fun, after all.
みんなとやってる... やっぱホロックスの活動ってなんか「ライブ」って感じじゃん？
Doing it with everyone... HoloX activities just feel like "Live", you know?
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロックサーがバーッているとこで出来るのが...
So being able to do that just us, with HoloXers everywhere...
嬉しいよな。
...is really happy.
嬉しい！
So happy!
いつも以上に熱いよ！
Hotter than usual!
いやだからもう俺たち本当にいろいろあったけど、これからも本当に...
So, we've really been through a lot, but from now on...
４人いれば大丈夫だから。頑張ろう。
...as long as the four of us are here, we're good. Let's do this.
頑張ろう！一致団結するぞ！
Let's do this! United as one!
頑張るぞー！
Let's do our best!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
速報です。トレンド１位ということで。
Breaking news. We're #1 trending.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ここから４月２９日までもうね、止まらねぇぞで、マインドに入れまくっててください。
From here to April 29th, we won't stop, so keep that in your mind.
はい！ということで改めて...
Yes! So, once again...
秘密結社holoX 1st Live 「First Mission」は...
Secret Society holoX 1st Live "First Mission"...
2026年4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
...will be held on April 29, 2026, at PIA ARENA MM!
空けとけ空けとけー！
Keep your schedule open!
諸々の詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので...
Details will be announced at a later date...
皆さん、続報を待っててござる！
Everyone, wait for the follow-up report!
よろしくお願いします！
Please!
そしてそして、先ほど聴いていただきました新曲...
And also, the new song you just heard...
「ゴウワンX」です！
It's "Gouwan X"!
公開したいと思います！
I'd like to reveal it!
イェーイ！
Yay!
おお！おしゃれですね！
Ooh! It's so stylish!
かっこいいね！
It's so cool!
そして...
And...
本日24時ですね...
Today at 24:00...
12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので...
The digital release will start at 0:00 on December 2nd...
ライブに向けてたくさん聴いてくれよな！
So please listen to it a lot for the live concert!
いや、もうコールできるとこいっぱいだからね！
Yeah, there are tons of parts where you can do calls!
聴くんだよ！
Listen to it!
めちゃめちゃもう... ライブのための曲みたいな...
It's seriously... like a song made for live performances...
X！X！
X! X!
お前ら予習して聴いて！
You guys, prepare and listen!
まだ新曲いっぱい聴いて、予習して...
Listen to the new song a lot more, prepare for it...
ライブ楽しみに待っててほしい！
And look forward to the live concert!
そしてアルバム『Secret Order』を持って！
Also, bring the album 'Secret Order'!
持って！持って！
Bring it! Bring it!
割れないように気をつけてね！
Be careful not to break it!
運ばなきゃ！持って来てね！
Gotta carry it! Bring it with you!
ライブ来てね！聴いて予習してね！
Come to the live! Listen and prepare!
アルバムは22時から販売開始です！
Album sales start at 22:00!
みんな買ってね！
Everyone, please buy it!
ホロックスのみんな...
Everyone in holoX...
え、本当に、夜遅くまでありがとう！
Um, really, thank you for staying up late!
見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for watching!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
来年はもう、ホロックスの...
Next year will be holoX's...
我々の年にしていくので！
We're going to make it our year!
頑張ろうね！
Let's do our best!
5年目もよろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well in our 5th year too!
お願いします！
Please!
じゃあみんな、せーのでいくよ！
Alright everyone, on 'se-no'!
せーの、バイバーイ！
Se-no, Bye-bye!
解散！解散！解散！
Dismissed! Dismissed! Dismissed!
やったー！やったー！
Yay! Yay!
気をつけて！気をつけて！バイバーイ！
Be careful! Be careful! Bye-bye!